( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Lin Juan has already taken down the ninth challenger.
لقد تمكن لين جوان بالفعل من هزيمة المنافس التاسع.
Does anyone else want to challenge?
هل يرغب أحد آخر في التحدي؟
Congratulations.
تهانينا.
Here is your prize.
هذه جائزتك.
I thought the prize was the fragment.
ظننت أن الجائزة هي القطعة.
That one?
هذا؟
That prize costs you your life.
تلك الجائزة تكلفك حياتك.
Are we really using the same way to get in again?
هل نستخدم نفس الطريقة للدخول مرة أخرى؟
Unless you want to get ambushed again.
إلا إذا كنت ترغب في التعرض لكمين مرة أخرى.
So what is our next step?
إذن ما هي خطوتنا التالية؟
It's been an exhausting day.
لقد كان يوماً مرهقاً.
Let's dodge everything for one night and relax.
دعونا نتجنب كل شيء لليلة واحدة ونسترخي.
I'll scratch your back to help you loosen up.
سأقوم بتدليك ظهرك لمساعدتك على الاسترخاء.
You really don't have to.
ليس عليك فعل ذلك حقاً.
A little scratch before bed.
حكّة خفيفة قبل النوم.
It's relaxing and good for you.
إنه مريح ومفيد لك.
Never heard of that?
ألم تسمع بهذا من قبل؟
Is this okay?
هل هذا مناسب؟
A little to the left.
قليلاً إلى اليسار.
Left.
غادر.
How does the pressure feel?
كيف تشعر بالضغط؟
A bit more to the left.
قليلاً إلى اليسار.
More to the left.
أكثر إلى اليسار.
Right there.
هنا بالضبط.
The owner of that boxing gym is Lu Ziye.
مالك صالة الملاكمة تلك هو لو زيي.
After pulling an all-nighter, he comes here every day
بعد أن سهر طوال الليل، يأتي إلى هنا كل يوم
for a bowl of hot soup.
من أجل وعاء من الحساء الساخن.
We'll wait and catch him then.
سننتظر ونقبض عليه حينها.
Talk to him first.
تحدث إليه أولاً.
Don't drink it.
لا تشربه.
The water tastes strange.
طعم الماء غريب.
This place isn't the real deal.
هذا المكان ليس المكان الحقيقي.
Let's go somewhere else.
لنذهب إلى مكان آخر.
[WANTED BEAD OR AIVE]
[مطلوب خرزة أو أيف]
Looks like they're coming after me.
يبدو أنهم يلاحقونني.
We should split up for now.
ينبغي أن ننفصل في الوقت الحالي.
Have Lin Juan stay and cover you.
اجعل لين جوان تبقى وتغطيك.
I'll make sure you get back safely.
سأحرص على عودتك سالماً.
Be careful.
احرص.
Don't go too hard on them.
لا تقسو عليهم كثيراً.
Go.
يذهب.
Come out.
يخرج.
Take me to your boss.
خذني إلى رئيسك.
Nongyu, over here.
نونغيو، تعال إلى هنا.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Mr. Wu sent me.
أرسلني السيد وو.
His watch picked up signs that.
رصدت ساعته إشارات تدل على ذلك.
Nongyu might be in danger around this area.
قد يكون نونغيو في خطر في هذه المنطقة.
I was nearby at the time.
كنتُ قريباً في ذلك الوقت.
So he sent me over to help.
فأرسلني للمساعدة.
Go help Xie Xinxu first.
اذهب لمساعدة Xie Xinxu أولاً.
Mr. Gu.
السيد غو.
If you do not form a pact with me today,
إذا لم تعقد معي اتفاقاً اليوم،
I will go out and tell everyone
سأخرج وأخبر الجميع
that you are a Ren.
أنك رين.
Hahahaha.
ههههههه.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
The owner of that boxing gym your friend went to
صاحب صالة الملاكمة التي كان صديقك يذهب إليها
is my husband.
هو زوجي.
Welcome to
أهلا وسهلا بكم
my Mugang.
يا موغانغي.
Your Mugang?
موغانغ خاصتك؟
I forgot to tell you.
نسيت أن أخبرك.
My mother is the head of the Special Administration Bureau.
والدتي هي رئيسة مكتب الإدارة الخاصة.
Most of this place is her business.
معظم هذا المكان ملكها.
I just help her
أنا فقط أساعدها
manage it for now.
تدبر الأمر في الوقت الحالي.
So,
لذا،
So you put out a warrant for me because I crossed into your illicit operations?
إذن أصدرتم مذكرة توقيف بحقي لأنني دخلت في عملياتكم غير المشروعة؟
Of course it was because I wanted to see you.
بالطبع كان ذلك لأني أردت رؤيتك.
My people
شعبي
said they spotted you,
قالوا إنهم رصدوك،
so I issued the warrant right away to find you.
لذلك أصدرت أمر التفتيش على الفور للعثور عليك.
How do you think your husband would feel
كيف تعتقدين أن زوجك سيشعر؟
if he heard that?
ماذا لو سمع ذلك؟
Is it appropriate?
هل هذا مناسب؟
That useless husband of mine
زوجي عديم الفائدة
is nothing more than a blood supply.
ليس الأمر أكثر من مجرد إمداد دموي.
You are the only one I like.
أنت الشخص الوحيد الذي يعجبني.
Sorry.
آسف.
I have no interest in you at all.
ليس لدي أي اهتمام بك على الإطلاق.
I was going to keep you here a couple more days.
كنت أنوي إبقاءك هنا لبضعة أيام أخرى.
But my mother was right.
لكن أمي كانت على حق.
Men
الرجال
are all the same.
كلها متشابهة.
Building a career is what really matters.
إن بناء مسيرة مهنية هو الأمر المهم حقاً.
The news about the third fragment was fake.
كانت الأخبار المتعلقة بالجزء الثالث مزيفة.
My mother only used it as bait
لم تستخدمه أمي إلا كطعم.
to take you,
لأخذك،
Wu Siyuan,
وو سيوان,
and everyone connected to you out.
وكل من كان على اتصال بك يغادر.
Lin Juan managed to dodge it last time.
تمكنت لين جوان من تفاديها في المرة الماضية.
That one?
هذا؟
That was meant to be traded for your life.
كان من المفترض أن يتم استبدال ذلك بحياتك.
But this time,
لكن هذه المرة،
we are fully prepared.
نحن على أتم الاستعداد.
I suppose.
أفترض.
Secretary Zhang
السكرتير تشانغ
has already picked up Wu Nongyu.
وقد تم التعاقد بالفعل مع وو نونغيو.
[Lu Ziye]
[لو زيي]
What do you mean by useless husband?
ماذا تقصدين بزوج عديم الفائدة؟
You planted people around me again, didn't you?
لقد زرعت أشخاصاً حولي مرة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
You must look awful right now.
لا بد أنك تبدو في حالة يرثى لها الآن.
If you're too ugly,
إذا كنت قبيحًا جدًا،
I won't even bother
لن أكلف نفسي عناء ذلك
letting you live off me.
أتركك تعيش على حسابي.
[Xu]
[Xu]
Nongyu, I'm sorry.
نونغيو، أنا آسف.
But I can't let you and Mr. Wu bring down the Bureau.
لكن لا يمكنني السماح لك وللسيد وو بإسقاط المكتب.
What are you going to do to me?
ماذا ستفعل بي؟
This area of Mugang has a complex mix of people.
تتميز هذه المنطقة من موغان بتنوع سكاني معقد.
There have been cases of escaped Ren
وقد سُجلت حالات هروب لرين
banding together to commit robberies.
التكاتف لارتكاب عمليات السطو.
If you die at their hands,
إذا متّ على أيديهم،
it would be good for all of us.
سيكون ذلك جيداً لنا جميعاً.
Back off.
تراجع.
Nobody move.
لا أحد يتحرك.
Hands up.
ارفعوا أيديكم.
Everyone stay still.
ابقوا جميعاً في مكانكم.
Keep making noise and I'll shoot you.
استمر في إحداث الضوضاء وسأطلق عليك النار.
Get down.
انزل.
Come out on your own.
اخرج بمفردك.
Come out.
يخرج.
Out of the car.
انزل من السيارة.
Now.
الآن.
Turn around yourself.
استدر حول نفسك.
Hands.
الأيدي.
Move.
يتحرك.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Behave.
تصرف بشكل لائق.
Take the latest inhibitor and the Yin with you.
خذ معك أحدث مثبطات الطاقة والين.
Yes.
نعم.
Nobody move.
لا أحد يتحرك.
Behave.
تصرف بشكل لائق.
Untie her hands.
فكّ قيود يديها.
Hello, Wei.
مرحباً، وي.
Calling Ye.
نداء إلى يي.
[Calling Ye…]
[أدعوكم…]
So noisy.
صاخب جداً.
We just got robbed.
لقد تعرضنا للسرقة للتو.
And the Yin we brought was taken.
وقد أُخذ الين الذي أحضرناه.
Go find them.
اذهب وابحث عنهم.
On my turf,
على أرضي،
no one takes anything from me.
لا أحد يأخذ مني شيئاً.
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
Go sit and wait.
اذهب واجلس وانتظر.
It will be over soon.
سينتهي الأمر قريباً.
No.
لا.
It's my birthday today.
اليوم عيد ميلادي.
And this dinner is all you prepared?
وهذا كل ما أعددته من عشاء؟
No gift?
لا توجد هدية؟
There is.
هنالك.
In this pocket.
في هذا الجيب.
There's no other gift.
لا توجد هدية أخرى.
It's just the watch vibrating.
إنها مجرد اهتزازات الساعة.
I wanted you to take it out and check.
أردت منك أن تخرجه وتفحصه.
[SOS Wu Nongyu]
[نداء استغاثة، أنت تعرف]
Nongyu seems to be in danger.
يبدو أن نونغيو في خطر.
She's not here.
إنها ليست هنا.
[Wu]
[وو]
Are you with Nongyu right now?
هل أنت مع نونغيو الآن؟
Secretary Zhang lured her away.
استدرجها السكرتير تشانغ بعيدًا.
Most likely,
على الأرجح،
she acted under Xia Shang's orders and is going after her.
لقد تصرفت بناءً على أوامر شيا شانغ وهي تلاحقها.
Her watch sent me a location.
أرسلت لي ساعتها موقعها.
Find her first.
ابحث عنها أولاً.
What exactly was going on with that group just now?
ما الذي كان يحدث بالضبط مع تلك المجموعة قبل قليل؟
I've already notified Siyuan.
لقد أبلغت سيوان بالفعل.
Let's find a place to hide for now.
لنبحث عن مكان للاختباء فيه الآن.
[Emergency contact is 83 km away]
[رقم الاتصال في حالات الطوارئ يبعد 83 كم]
So this is where you were hiding.
إذن هذا هو المكان الذي كنت تختبئ فيه.
The scent of Yin.
رائحة الين.
Judging by the silhouette, looks like a handsome guy.
يبدو من خلال شكله الخارجي أنه رجل وسيم.
I can't hold back anymore, girls.
لم أعد أستطيع كبح جماحي يا فتيات.
Out of bullets.
نفدت الذخيرة.
Perfect.
ممتاز.
So the two of you came together to die?
إذن، اجتمعتما معاً للموت؟
No.
لا.
Don't get in the way.
لا تعترض الطريق.
Not bad, that manhole cover.
غطاء فتحة الصرف الصحي هذا ليس سيئاً.
That's just a lousy medal from that underground boxing match.
إنها مجرد ميدالية رديئة من مباراة الملاكمة السرية تلك.
Well then,
حسناً إذاً،
my baby has a fun new toy.
طفلي لديه لعبة جديدة ممتعة.
Lin Juan.
لين جوان.
♪ You smell like something strange ♪
♪ رائحتك غريبة ♪
♪ Like wood ♪
♪ مثل الخشب ♪
♪ Like wine ♪
♪ مثل النبيذ ♪
♪ Like the fading rain ♪
♪ مثل المطر المتلاشي ♪
♪ It's not a problem I can fix ♪
♪ إنها ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها ♪
♪ Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy… ♪
♪ ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بين يديكِ… ♪
Brothers.
إخوة.
Bring out your babies.
أخرجوا أطفالكم.
Don't let them get away!
لا تدعهم يهربون!
Let's split it.
لنقسمها.
Half and half.
نصف ونصف.
You can have it all.
يمكنك الحصول على كل شيء.
Right on time.
في الموعد المحدد تماماً.
♪ The touch of your warm embrace ♪
♪ لمسة حضنك الدافئ ♪
♪ I'm a slave to you ♪
♪ أنا عبدٌ لك ♪
♪ Can you feel that you're my fire? ♪
♪ هل تشعر أنك ناري؟ ♪
♪ Listening to your whispers, wrapped in your dangerous presence ♪
♪ أستمع إلى همساتك، محاطًا بحضورك الخطير ♪
♪ The touch of your warm embrace ♪
♪ لمسة حضنك الدافئ ♪
♪ I'm a slave to you ♪
♪ أنا عبدٌ لك ♪
♪ Can you feel that you're my fire? ♪
♪ هل تشعر أنك ناري؟ ♪
♪ You smell like something strange ♪
♪ رائحتك غريبة ♪
♪ Like wood ♪
♪ مثل الخشب ♪
♪ Like wine ♪
♪ مثل النبيذ ♪
♪ Like the fading rain ♪
♪ مثل المطر المتلاشي ♪
♪ It's not a problem I can fix ♪
♪ إنها ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها ♪
♪ Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy ♪
♪ ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بين يديك ♪